[Music]
hey guys
pastor myers here and uh this is the
first episode
of i got a question
and today i'm going to be answering two
questions
so the first question is this what are
your thoughts about the pros and cons of
masks and social distancing right now
i live in blank blank and i'm trying to
be as safe as possible
but i really miss being social and going
to church
there's only two people myself and
another person wearing a mask
at work and i've been invited to social
events
but i have kindly rejected i'm starting
to wonder if i'm still on the right
track
also want to be a witness for god and i
sometimes feel selfish of staying home
what are your thoughts so
uh my thoughts are wear a mask
and uh don't feel pressure by people
you know think like leading you to think
oh you're being selfish or
you're being afraid or anything like
that because of wearing a mask
i think the safe thing to do is wear a
mask
you would rather be safe than sorry
you're not only thinking about yourself
but you think about the health of others
so you know from what i understand you
can actually
have covid and be symptom-free but pass
it to someone else
so um you know personally i'm wearing a
mask
not only for my safety but
because i'm thinking about other people
as well and you can still be a witness
with a mask
right mass has to do with whether you're
able to witness for god or not
be safe and uh and take precautions
because you would rather
be safe than sorry so the second
question is i was wondering about the
seven churches of bible prophecy
of the book of revelation how do we know
whether these churches
represent periods of time throughout
history or if they represent
one period of time and that is during
the early church
during the apostles so the answer to
this question is
relatively simple although we can pack
it
unpack it a whole lot more but i'm just
going to
try to juice this down as best i can so
when you look at the book of revelation
and you look at these seven churches
they represent
a cycle of time so if you
go back to the very first time you have
this series of one through seven
it's in the book of genesis right the
seven days of creation
those seven days the week represents a
progression
of time so when you get to the book of
revelation and you have the seven
churches the seven seals
and these seven trumpets they represent
a progression
of time it's not happening
simultaneously the week was not created
simultaneously
it was day one day two day three so on
and so forth
so when we get to the book of revelation
and we're looking at these seven
churches
these seven churches represent a
progression of time
and what we would want to know is when
does this cycle begin
and when does it end and the very first
church would represent the apostolic age
the very last church the church of
laodicea
which by the way means the people of the
judgment
would symbolize the very last church at
the end of time
that is living or will live just in the
time of the judgment
before jesus comes again so
uh for that reason i believe that these
seven churches
represent a progression of time from the
time of
uh jesus's death burial and resurrection
the day of pentecost
the early church all the way to the
second coming
of jesus there is the answer
to your question so to submit your
question and it can be a question on
anything it can be bible prophecy it
could be
you know personal whatever to submit
your question
text 866-463-5262
or simply 866 god lamb
l-a-n-b god lamb also be sure to follow
me
on instagram at ivorymeyers and i will
see you in the next episode of
i got a question